Robert A. Taft Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1946-1953 (Box 871-1284)
  - 1950 (Box 914)
    - Patents
    - Pensions
    - Photographs
    - Political
      - Republican, (4 folders)
    - Positions (Box 921)
    - Presidency
    - Public Relations
    - Puerto Rico
    - Reciprocal Trade Agreements
    - Recommendations
    - Reorganization
    - Republican National Committee
    - Rubber
    - Rural Electrification Administration
    - Schorr, Edward
    - Senate bills (numbers)
    - Senators
    - Social Security
    - Soil Conservation
    - Sokolsky, George
    - Spain
    - Speakers
    - State Department (Box 922)
    - Steel
    - Steering committee
    - Strikes
    - Subsidies
    - Tariff
    - Tax exemptions
    - Taxes
      - Excess Profits, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 923)
    - Thank You Letters
      - Taft, Martha Bowers, (2 folders)
    - Truman, Harry S.
    - Umstatt, William E.
    - Unemployment compensation
    - United Nations
    - Veteran (Box 924)
      - Army Times
      - Miscellaneous
      - Schools
    - Visitors
    - Voting
    - War, Korean
    - Yugoslavia
  - 1951 (Box 925)
    - Administration
    - Administrative assistants and secretaries
    - Agriculture, (2 folders)
    - Aid to Europe
    - Air force
      - “A-D” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - “E-H” miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 926)
      - “I-S” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 927)
      - “S-Z” miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 928)
    - Airports
    - Alaska
    - Allotments, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 929)
    - Appointments
      - General, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 930)
  - Executive, (2 folders) (Box 931)
    - Appropriation, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 932)
    - Armed services
      - First Part, (3 folders)
      - Second Part, (4 folders); (2 folders) (Box 933, Box 934)
    - Army assignments
      - A-D, (2 folders)
      - E-R, (4 folders) (Box 935)
      - S-Z, (2 folders) (Box 936)
    - Army complaints
      - General, (2 folders); (4 folders); (5 folders) (Box 937, Box 938)
    - Army (Box 939)
      - General, (4 folders)
      - Negroes
    - Articles
      - General, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 940)
      - Sent to Taft, (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box 941)
      - Statements requested of Taft, (5 folders) (Box 942)
    - Article and statement about Taft (Box 943)
    - Atomic bomb
    - Autographs, (2 folders)
    - Aviation
    - Awards
    - Banking
    - Bids (Box 944)
      - Government, (4 folders)
    - Biography (Taft) (Box 945)
    - Bonds
    - Book
      - A Foreign Policy for Americans
      - Galley
      - Lists of copies sent
      - Requests for Autographs
      - Reviews, (2 folders)
    - Books and booklets sent to Taft, (5 folders); (1 folder) (Box 946, Box 947)
    - Budget
    - Business
    - Butter
    - Casualties, (2 folders) (Box 948)
    - Cemeteries
    - Census
    - China
    - Christmas cards
    - Cincinnati, Ohio
    - Citizenship
    - Civil Aeronautics Administration
    - Civil Defense Administration
    - Civil rights
    - Civil service, (2 folders) (Box 949)
    - Claims
      - A-D, (2 folders)
      - E-Z, (6 folders) (Box 950)
    - Clippings (Box 951)
    - Coals
    - Coast guard
    - Commentators
    - Commerce Department
    - Commissions, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 952)
    - Committees
    - Commodity Credit Corp. (Box 953)
    - Communism, (3 folders)
    - Communists
    - Condolences
    - Congratulations, (1 folder) (Box 954)
    - Congress
    - Congress, Library of
    - Congressional Directory
    - Congressional Record
    - Conscientious objectors
    - Contributions, (1 folder) (Box 955)
    - Controls
      - A-D, (4 folders)
      - E-K, (4 folders) (Box 956)
      - L-R, (5 folders) (Box 957)
      - S-Z, (4 folders) (Box 958)
    - Conventions
    - Cooperatives
    - Cost of living
    - Cotton
    - Course in Senate, (3 folders) (Box 959)
    - Courts-martial
      - “A-H” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - “I-Z” miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 960)
    - Currency
    - Customs
    - Czechoslovakia
    - Defense Production Act
    - Deferments
      - A-B, (2 folders)
      - C-N, (4 folders) (Box 961)
      - O-Z, (3 folders) (Box 962)
    - Desvernine, Raoul E.
    - Displaced persons
    - District of Columbia
    - Draft, (1 folder) (Box 963)
    - Economic Cooperation Administration
    - Economic report, Joint Committee on
    - Education, (2 folders)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
    - Elections
    - Emanuel, Victor, (2 folders) (Box 964)
    - Engagements, (2 folders); (5 folders); (4 folders) (Box 965, Box 966)
    - England
    - Equal rights
    - Exports and imports
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (Box 967)
    - Farm Credit Administration
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Federal Communications Commission, (2 folders)
    - Federal
    - Federal Housing Administration
    - Federal Power Commission
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - Federal Security Agency
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Finance
    - Fisheries
    - Flag
    - Floods and flood control, (2 folders) (Box 968)
    - Food
    - Football tickets
    - Foreign policy
      - General, (3 folders)
      - A-C, (4 folders) (Box 969)
      - C-G, (5 folders) (Box 970)
      - H-L, (5 folders) (Box 971)
      - M-R, (5 folders) (Box 972)
      - S-Z, (5 folders) (Box 973)
    - Furloughs (Box 974)
    - Gallery passes
    - Gas
    - Germany
    - Gifts, (2 folders)
    - Gold
    - Government Printing Office
    - Greece
    - Hawaii (Box 975)
    - Health, (2 folders)
    - Highways
    - Home Owners Loan Corp.
    - Hoover, Herbert
    - Hospitals
    - House joint resolutions
    - House of Representatives
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Bills (Box 976)
        - Nos. 2-4999, (2 folders)
        - Nos. 4000-5999, (2 folders) (Box 977)
    - Housing, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 978, Box 979)
    - Hurley case, 1951-1952
    - Immigration, (4 folders); (9 folders); (8 folders) (Box 980, Box 981)
    - India, (2 folders) (Box 982)
    - Indians
    - Inflation
    - Insurance, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 983)
    - Interior, Department of
    - Internal Revenue Service, (2 folders)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Introductory letters
    - Invitations declined (Box 984)
      - General, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 985)
      - A-C, (4 folders)
      - D-M, (10 folders) (Box 986)
      - N-S, (5 folders) (Box 987)
      - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box 988)
    - Israel
    - Italy
    - Japan
    - Jews
    - Justice Department, (2 folders) (Box 989)
    - Keller, O. E. M.
    - Julius, Klein, (3 folders)
    - Labor (Box 990)
      - A-D, (5 folders)
      - E-L, (5 folders) (Box 991)
      - M-R, (4 folders) (Box 992)
      - S-Z, (5 folders) (Box 993)
    - Labor Department
    - Labor legislation (Box 994)
      - “A-Z “ miscellaneous
      - Public Welfare Commission
      - Unions
    - Legislation
      - Miscellaneous
        - A-H, (2 folders)
        - I-Z, (3 folders) (Box 995)
    - Licenses
    - Lists
    - Loans
    - Lobbying
    - MacArthur, Douglas A., (2 folders)
    - Mall
    - Marine Corps (Box 996)
      - A-S, (4 folders)
      - T-Z (Box 997)
    - Maritime commission
    - Marshall, John
    - Martin, Jack I.
      - General
      - Personal, (2 folders)
    - Medical care
    - Membership, (2 folders)
    - Merchant marines
    - Military discharges (Box 998)
      - A-B, (4 folders)
      - B-C, (4 folders) (Box 999)
      - C-D, (5 folders) (Box 1000)
      - E-G, (7 folders) (Box 1001)
      - G-H, (8 folders) (Box 1002)
      - H-J, (6 folders) (Box 1003)
      - K-L, (7 folders) (Box 1004)
      - L-M, (5 folders) (Box 1005)
      - M, (6 folders) (Box 1006)
      - N-R, (7 folders) (Box 1007)
      - R-S, (5 folders) (Box 1008)
      - S, (5 folders) (Box 1009)
      - S-V, (6 folders) (Box 1010)
      - W-Z, (8 folders) (Box 1011)
    - Milk (Box 1012)
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - A-B, (2 folders)
      - B-C, (4 folders) (Box 1013)
      - D-G, (5 folders) (Box 1014)
      - H-K, (5 folders) (Box 1015)
      - K-N, (5 folders) (Box 1016)
      - O-R, (4 folders) (Box 1017)
      - S-T, (4 folders) (Box 1018)
      - U-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1019)
      - Notes
    - Monetary
    - National defense
    - National guard
    - National parks
    - National (Box 1020)
    - National Production Authority, (4 folders)
    - National Production Authority (Box 1021)
    - National Alside Aluminum Co.
    - National Adamson Co.
    - Navy
      - A-D, (3 folders)
      - E-L, (6 folders) (Box 1022)
      - M-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1023)
    - Negroes
    - Newspapers
    - Office details, (2 folders) (Box 1024)
    - Office of Price Administration
      - Act
      - Rent control, (2 folders) (Box 1025)
    - Ohio State matters
      - A-D
      - E-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1026)
    - Oil
    - O'Berg, Blanche
    - Pages (Box 1027)
    - Palestine
    - Panama Canal
    - Paper
    - Patents
    - Peace
    - Pensions
      - “A-C” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - “D-L” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 1028)
      - “M-T” miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 1029)
      - “W-Z” miscellaneous (Box 1030)
      - Plans
    - Philippines
    - Photographs, (2 folders)
    - Poland (Box 1031)
    - Policy committee
    - Political
      - General
        - A-C, (3 folders)
        - D-J, (5 folders) (Box 1032)
        - K-P, (4 folders) (Box 1033)
        - R-Z, (5 folders) (Box 1034)
      - Republican (Box 1035)
        - A-C, (5 folders)
        - D-H, (4 folders) (Box 1036)
        - H-M, (5 folders) (Box 1037)
        - M-S, (5 folders) (Box 1038)
        - S-W, (4 folders) (Box 1039)
        - W-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1040)
      - Taft
        - A-C, (3 folders)
        - D-J, (5 folders) (Box 1041)
        - L-S, (6 folders) (Box 1042)
        - S-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1043)
    - Positions
      - A-B, (2 folders)
      - C-G, (5 folders) (Box 1044)
      - H-M, (7 folders) (Box 1045)
      - M-S, (6 folders) (Box 1046)
      - S-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1047)
    - Post offices, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 1048)
    - Postmasters
    - Presidency
    - Private bills, (2 folders) (Box 1049)
      - Grossu, Mircea, S. 77
      - Heller, Herbert H., S. 76
      - Sato, Georgette William, S. 1499
    - Projects
    - Promotions
    - Public works
    - Publications
      - A
      - B-C, (4 folders) (Box 1050)
      - C-F, (5 folders) (Box 1051)
      - G-I, (5 folders) (Box 1052)
      - J-Mc, (6 folders) (Box 1053)
      - M-P, (6 folders) (Box 1054)
      - Q-S, (6 folders) (Box 1055)
      - S-W, (5 folders) (Box 1056)
      - W-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1057)
    - Radio
    - Railroad retirement, (2 folders)
    - Railroads
    - Rationing (Box 1058)
    - Reciprocal trade agreements, (2 folders)
    - Recommendations, (2 folders)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp., (1 folder) (Box 1059)
    - Red Cross
    - Religion
    - Reorganization plans
    - Republican National Committee
    - Reservations and tickets
    - Retirement, (2 folders)
      - Haddad, Edward G.
    - Retirement legislation
    - Rivers and harbors (Box 1060)
    - Rubber
    - Rural Electrification Administration
    - Russia
    - Saint Lawrence, (1 folder) (Box 1061)
    - School lunches
    - Securities and Exchange Commission
    - Selective Service Act, (3 folders)
    - Selective Service System, (2 folders) (Box 1062)
    - Senate bills
      - Nos. 0-999, (2 folders)
      - Nos. 0-999 (Box 1063)
      - Nos. 1000-1999, (4 folders)
      - Nos. 1000-1999 (Box 1064)
      - Nos. 2000-4999
    - Senate resolutions
    - Senators, correspondence about and with, (2 folders)
    - Small business
    - Social legislation
    - Social security, (4 folders) (Box 1065)
    - Soil conservation
    - Sokolsky, George (Box 1066)
    - South America
    - Spain
    - Speakers
    - Speech comments, (3 folders)
    - Speeches (Box 1067)
      - Copies requested, (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1068)
      - Received from others, (2 folders)
    - State Department, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1069)
    - Steel
    - Strikes
    - Subsidies
    - Sugar
    - Supreme Court
    - Taft-Martin
    - Taft, Martha Bowers
      - General
      - Thank you letters
    - Tariff, (2 folders)
    - Tate, Ben E. (Box 1070)
    - Tax
      - Capital gains
      - Cooperatives, (4 folders)
      - Excess profits (Box 1071)
      - Excise, (2 folders)
      - Exemptions, (2 folders)
      - General, (5 folders) (Box 1072)
      - Hall, E.O. (Box 1073)
      - Income, (4 folders)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 1074)
      - Refund
      - Sales
      - Withholding
    - Tennessee Valley Authority
    - Television
    - Tobacco
    - Townsend Plan
    - Trade
    - Trade agreements
    - Trade marks
    - Transfers, (2 folders) (Box 1075)
    - Transportation
    - Treasury
    - Treaties
    - Truman, Harry S.
    - Unemployment compensation
    - United Nations (Box 1076)
    - Veterans
      - General, (1 folder) (Box 1077)
      - Legislation, (2 folders)
    - Visitors, (2 folders)
    - Voting (Box 1078)
    - Walter, Paul
    - War
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Material, disposal of
    - Washington, D.C., office
    - Water
    - Wheat
    - Wool
    - Younger, Cole J.
    - Yugoslavia
  - 1952 (Box 1079)
    - Academies
    - Administration
    - Agriculture, (2 folders)
    - Air force
      - A-D, (3 folders)
      - F-M, (6 folders) (Box 1080)
      - M-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1081)
    - Airports
    - Alaska
    - Allotments, (2 folders) (Box 1082)
    - Appointments
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Executive, (3 folders) (Box 1083)
    - Appropriations, (2 folders) (Box 1084)
    - Armed services, (2 folders)
    - Army assignments
      - A-D
      - E-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1085)
    - Army (Box 1086)
      - Complaints, (2 folders)
      - General
        - A-C, (3 folders)
        - D-M, (6 folders) (Box 1087)
        - T-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1088)
    - Articles sent to Taft
      - General, (2 folders) (Box 1089)
      - “A-N” miscellaneous, (4 folders)
      - “O-Z” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 1090)
      - Statements, about
      - Request of, (4 folders) (Box 1091)
      - McCarthyism
    - Atomic bomb (Box 1092)
    - Atomic Energy Commission
      - General
      - Portsmouth Project, general
    - Austria
    - Autographs, A-Z, (4 folders)
    - Aviation (Box 1093)
    - Awards
    - Banking
    - Bids, government, (3 folders)
    - Bills, expenses
    - Biography
    - Bonds (Box 1094)
    - Books
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Reviews
      - “B-G” miscellaneous, (2 folders)
      - “H-Z” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 1095)
    - Broadcasting
    - Budget, (3 folders) (Box 1096)
    - Canada
    - Cancer
    - Casualties
    - Census
    - China (Box 1097)
    - Christmas
    - Cincinnati, Ohio
    - Citizenship
    - Civil rights
    - Civil service
    - Claims
      - “A-B” miscellaneous
      - “C-Z” miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 1098)
    - Clippings (Box 1099)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Martin, Jack I., (3 folders)
    - Coal (Box 1100)
    - Coast guard
    - Coffee
    - Commerce Department
    - Commission, A-Z, (4 folders)
    - Committees (Box 1101)
    - Commodity Credit Corp.
    - Communists
    - Compensation Commission
    - Compulsory military training
    - Condolences
    - Congratulations
      - A-F
      - G-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1102)
    - Congress
    - Congress, Library of
    - Congressional Directory
    - Congressional Record
    - Contributions
      - A-F
      - G-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1103)
    - Controls
      - A-S, (4 folders)
      - T-Z (Box 1104)
    - Cost of living
    - Cotton
    - Course in Senate
    - Courts-martial, A-Z, (6 folders)
    - Currency (Box 1105)
    - Customs
    - Deferments, (2 folders)
    - Desvernine, Raoul E.
    - Displaced persons
    - District of Columbia
    - Draft
    - Economic Report, Joint Committee
    - Economic Stabilization Agency
    - Education, (2 folders) (Box 1106)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., (2 folders) (Box 1107)
    - Elections
    - Electoral College
    - Electricity
    - Emanuel, Victor, (2 folders) (Box 1108)
    - Employment
    - Engagements
      - General, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 1109)
      - Author meets the critics
    - Equal rights
    - Exports and imports
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (Box 1110)
    - Fair trade
    - Farm Security Administration
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - Federal Communication Commission, (2 folders)
    - Federal Housing Administration
    - Federal Power Commission
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - Federal Security Agency (Box 1111)
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Fellers, Bonner
    - Floods and flood control
      - General
      - Mahoning Grand River-Heard
    - Floor leader
    - Food
    - Football tickets
    - Foreign policy (Box 1112)
      - A-H, (5 folders)
      - I-Z, (5 folders) (Box 1113)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 1114)
    - Furloughs
    - Gallery panes
    - Germany
    - Gifts, A-Z, (2 folders)
    - Gold (Box 1115)
    - Government Printing Office
    - Great Britain
    - Greece
    - Guam
    - Hawaii
    - Health
    - Highways
    - Home Owners Loan Corp.
    - Hospitals
    - House of Representatives
      - Nos.0-3999
      - Nos. 4000-4999 (Box 1116)
      - Nos. 5000-5999
      - Nos. 6000-6999
      - Nos. 7000-7999 (Box 1117)
    - Housing
      - A-P, (3 folders)
      - R-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1118)
    - Hungary
    - Immigration
      - “A-G” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
      - “H-S” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 1119)
      - “S-Z” miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 1120)
      - McCarran-Walter Omnibus Bill (S 2550)
    - Inauguration
    - India
    - Indians
    - Inflation (Box 1121)
    - Insurance, A-Z, (3 folders)
    - Interior, Department of
    - Internal Revenue Service, (2 folders) (Box 1122)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
      - Hurley
    - Introductory letters
    - Invitations after July
    - Invitations declined (Box 1123)
      - “A-D” miscellaneous, (4 folders)
      - “A-L” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 1124)
      - League of Women Voters
      - “M-S” miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 1125)
      - “S-Z” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 1126)
      - Citizens view of
    - Japan (Box 1127)
    - Jews
    - Justice Department
    - Keller, O. E. M.
    - Klein, Julius, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 1128)
    - Labor
      - “A-C” miscellaneous, (3 folders)
      - “D-L” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 1129)
      - “M-S” miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 1130)
      - “T-Z” miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 1131)
      - Department
      - Legislation
        - A-H, (4 folders)
        - J-Z, (6 folders) (Box 1132)
      - Public Welfare Committee
      - Unions (Box 1133)
    - Land grants
    - Langer, William
    - Legislative miscellany, A-Z, (4 folders)
    - Licenses
    - Livestock
    - Loans
    - Lobbying
    - MacArthur, Douglas (Box 1134)
    - Mail
    - Marine Corps, A-Z, (5 folders)
    - Maritime Commission
    - Marshall, John
    - Membership
    - Memoranda
    - Merchant marines
    - Military discharges (Box 1135)
      - A-B, (4 folders)
      - C-E, (5 folders) (Box 1136)
      - F-H, (5 folders) (Box 1137)
      - H-L, (6 folders) (Box 1138)
      - L-P, (7 folders) (Box 1139)
      - O-S, (6 folders) (Box 1140)
      - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box 1141)
    - Milk (Box 1142)
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous
      - A-B, (4 folders)
      - C-E, (5 folders) (Box 1143)
      - F-H, (5 folders) (Box 1144)
      - H-Mc, (7 folders) (Box 1145)
      - M-R, (7 folders) (Box 1146)
      - R-S, (4 folders) (Box 1147)
      - T-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1148)
    - Monetary
    - Mutual Security Administration
    - National debt (Box 1149)
    - National defense
    - National Guard
    - National Production Authority
    - Navy
      - A-B
      - E-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1150)
    - Negroes
    - Newspapers (Box 1151)
    - Office Details
    - Office of Price Stabilization
      - A-P, (3 folders)
      - R-Z, (2 folders) (Box 1152)
    - Ohio, state matters
      - A-N, (3 folders)
      - O-Z (Box 1153)
    - Oil
    - Pages
    - Panama Canal
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Peace
    - Pensions (Box 1154)
      - A-P, (5 folders)
      - R-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1155)
    - Philippines
    - Photographs
      - A-H, (2 folders)
      - I-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1156)
    - Poland
    - Policy committee
    - Political (Box 1157)
      - General
        - A-C, (5 folders)
        - D-K, (5 folders) (Box 1158)
        - L–S, (6 folders) (Box 1159)
        - S-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1160)
      - Republican
        - A-B
        - B-C, (4 folders) (Box 1161)
        - D-F, (5 folders) (Box 1162)
        - G-J, (6 folders) (Box 1163)
        - K-M, (5 folders) (Box 1164)
        - M-P, (5 folders) (Box 1165)
        - P-S, (5 folders) (Box 1166)
        - S-W, (4 folders) (Box 1167)
        - W-Z, (3 folders) (Box 1168)
      - Taft
        - A-B
        - C-L, (4 folders) (Box 1169)
        - M-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1170)
    - Polls
    - Poll tax
    - Positions (Box 1171)
      - A-L, (11 folders)
      - M-Z, (7 folders) (Box 1172)
    - Postmasters (Box 1173)
    - Post offices, A-Z, (4 folders)
    - Post Office Department
    - Presidency
    - Private bills (Box 1174)
      - S. 1931, Joyce Jacqualyn Johnson
      - S. 3743, Masao Kinoshita
      - S. 1886, Hisae Kuramoto
      - S. 1281, Eric Adolf Lenze
      - S. 1282, relief of Cecil Lennox Elliott
      - S. 1196, to provide military status for women who served overseas with the army during World War I (McGarr)
      - S. 602, John B. H. Waring
      - S. 3058, Nessie S. Widler
    - Privileges and Elections Committee
    - Promotions
    - Public laws, miscellaneous
    - Public works
    - Publications (Box 1175)
      - A-C, (5 folders)
      - D-H, (5 folders) (Box 1176)
      - H-Mc, (6 folders) (Box 1177)
      - M-Q, (7 folders) (Box 1178)
      - R-S, (5 folders) (Box 1179)
      - T-Z, (4 folders) (Box 1180)
    - Puerto Rico
    - Radio (Box 1181)
    - Railroads
    - Railroad retirement
    - Reciprocal trade agreements
    - Recommendations
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp.
    - Red Cross
    - Religion
    - Reorganization plan, (1 folder) (Box 1182)
    - Republican National Committee
    - Republican National Convention
    - Republican Speakers Bureau, Washington, D.C.
    - Reservations and tickets
    - Retirement
    - Retirement legislation
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Rural Electrification Administration
    - Russia
    - St. Lawrence waterway (Box 1183)
    - Salaries
    - Securities Exchange Commission
    - Selective Service Act, (2 folders)
    - Selective service system
    - Senate bills
      - No. 999
      - Nos. 1000-5999, (4 folders) (Box 1184)
    - Senators
      - Correspondence about
      - Correspondence with
    - Shipping (Box 1185)
    - Small business
    - Social legislation
    - Social security
      - A-S miscellaneous, (6 folders)
      - T-Z miscellaneous (Box 1186)
    - Soil conservation
    - South America
    - Spain
    - Speakers
    - Speech comments
      - A-R, (3 folders)
      - S-Z (Box 1187)
    - Speeches, copies requested, (2 folders)
    - Speeches received from others, (2 folders)
    - Stassen, Harold E.
    - State Department, (2 folders) (Box 1188)
    - Steel
    - Steering Committee, Republican Policy Committee
    - Strikes
    - Subsides
    - Taft (Box 1189)
      - Martin, Jack I., correspondence
      - Taft, Martha Bowers
      - Taft, William Howard, A-Z, (4 folders)
    - Tariff (Box 1190)
    - Tate, Benjamin F.
    - Taxes
      - Capital gains
      - Cooperatives
      - Excess profits
      - Excise
      - Exemptions
      - General, (1 folder) (Box 1191)
      - Income